<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalProject</string>
    <string name="text_view">TextView</string>

    <string name="night_mode">Night Mode</string>
    <string name="day_mode">Day Mode</string>

    <string name="story_1">On Alpha 1, meteor strikes happen daily. </string>
    <string name="story_2">This is because many of it"'"s moons shattering due the strong gravitational pull of the planet.</string>
    <string name="story_3">The only protection this world has against these meteors is a crystal gem creating a magnetic field, destroying the debris before it hits the surface.</string>
    <string name="story_4">Your job is to make sure the crystal gem does NOT fall off its pedestal.</string>
    <string name="story_5">On this planet, meteor strikes happen daily. </string>
    <string name="story_6">Today, you just woke up and still feel a little tired. Do you want to go back to sleep, or get up? </string>
    <string name="wake_up">Wake up</string>
    <string name="sleep">Go back to Sleep</string>
    <string name="second_story1">Through the stiff muscles and your body begging you to go back to sleep you manage to get up.
        \nYou head downstairs to your cabin"'"s kitchen, deciding what you want to eat before you check in on the crystal.
        \nDo you want to grab an apple or just get on with your day?
    </string>
    <string name="end_world1">You decide to sleep in without checking on the crystal gem.
        \nLittle did you know, a gust of wind blew the gem off it"'"s pedestal.
        \nDue to your laziness, the daily meteor strike has destroyed Alpha 1 and soon all life on this  once bountiful planet will perish.
    </string>
    <string name="game_over_text">GAME OVER</string>
    <string name="eat_apple_text">Eat Apple</string>
    <string name="eat_nothing_text">Eat nothing</string>
    <string name="enter_password_here">Enter password here</string>
    <string name="third_story1">As you leave your cabin and walk the small distance to the gem"'"s pedestal, you happen to notice it has fallen to the ground.
        \nYou recall that if the gem stays on the ground too long, the meteor debris will destroy the planet.
        \nWhat do you do?
    </string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="replace_gem">Replace Gem</string>
    <string name="leave_gem">Leave Gem</string>
    <string name="third_story2">As you replace the gem, you hear a soft hum as a blue aura fills the sky.
            \nAs you look up, you can see the debris hitting what seems to be an invisible dome.
            \nThe debris is completely stopped in it"'"s tracks and Alpha 1 seems safe, for now.
    </string>
    <string name="starvation">As you replace the gem, you hear a soft hum as a blue aura fills the sky.
            \nAs you look up, you can see the debris hitting what seems to be an invisible dome.
            \nThe debris is completely stopped in it"'"s tracks and Alpha 1 seems safe, for now.
            \nAs you walk back to your cabin, the rumblings of your stomach prove to be too much for you as you pass out on the way back home…</string>
    <string name="leftgem">You decide the best course of action is to leave the gem alone for now.
            \nAs you walk back to your cabin, however, you take glance up to the sky as some meteor debris start falling towards Alpha 1.
            \nYour heart starts racing as it slowly gets bigger and bigger…
    </string>
</resources>